Hello Hello Friends Welcome Back To Galti
Express Express Your Wealth Creation
Friends In today's video I will
talk about four fundamentalism companies
Friends The business potential of these companies
in India Friends
In the coming time there is going to be a lot of anger
from these companies I am going to talk about FIR stage and Mutual Fund
Friends I have
bought a lot of goods in the last quarter so I will add some important things about these companies So
you guys do
not skip the video So watch this video till the end so that
you do not miss any important
information So friends let's
start Friends The first company is
HDFC Life Insurance Company The
market has all like 102 hedges four crores
and planets Friends there is no problem on
this company You can
see its shooting You have a tremendous holding of 21.6% on
this company
Right now it is a NAAC company Friends
Before telling about it Friends I would
request you If you are new to this channel then
please subscribe to this channel
and also press the notification bell icon
So friends here the next
company is SBI Life Insurance Company,
this company has a
huge holding of 25587 crores, think there is
no debt on this company also, friends
you can like and share, there is no problem,
now the next company here is
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company, friends there
is a huge holding of 5 crores on this company, its fans are
2339, the company also has a huge
holding of 30.8 percent and the mutual
fund also has a huge holding of 1046 percent on this
company and lastly the
company friends is ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance Company, the company has a huge holding of
6 crore, fat 32.30 percent and the
mutual fund has a
huge holding on this company and here
friends I am going to put a very important parameter in
front of the years, you should
check it quickly, you should see it,
from December quarter to March quarter the
paper, hence this pace has been further increased,
friends the speed has been further increased by 1.4 three percent from the
peak to 1.3  Of percent and
Mutual Fund friends, it has been increased to point 84 on
this Deep Sea Life Insurance,
so you can note this thing here,
that is where the market was crashing
FD, come let's increase your stake on this and Mutual Fund company,
you should keep an eye on this Aamir, along with this,
next company SBI Life Insurance,
friends have
reduced their stake on it at point 25, but
friends one and a half more mutual funds have kept their
stock high and from December to
March till the scare, next company
friends ICICI Lombard,
friends have reduced their stake on it by 5 percent,
and Mutual Fund friends have
increased their stake till the scare of distemper and mask,
now on Prudential Life Insurance from
6 am, friends have increased their stake to point
zero percent,
friends have increased their stake to point zero one
and Mutual Fund friends have reduced their stock by point 20%,
now on these companies,
friends, I am going to present a very important
article in front of you, please
check it quickly.  You should see their
cross return premium collection
from 2016
to 12th, here in 2016 they
had 350 educational institutions, Indian toilets in which
often the premium collection has
increased to 100% in 2019, friends,
now friends, there was an article on this,
you can read it by going to the Economic Times
website, so see here,
friends, friends, the penetration of insurance and all insurance in India right now
is point 169 till 2017, which was
earlier 2.7 crore in 2001, so you can imagine that
in such a big country, friends, our
population is above 10.305 crore, the
penetration of our insurance sector is just point sixty
nine percent, so there is going to be very important fruit
in the insurance sector in the times to come
and
see in the financial year 1918, now there is
growth in premium collection at 10.75 and
friends, I would like to show you one more thing  If you
look here, in the market, if you look at
2 minutes, in the insurance sector, LIC has a
market share of 5228 percent,
friends, the next company Edifice is at second place,
Standard Life, SBI
Life Insurance, ICICI Prudential
and Adarsh, all four of these are
big companies, friends. My
purpose behind presenting these articles in front of you is that
friends, there is still a
lot of growth potential in the insurance sector in the coming time,
so
you should study these four insurance companies thoroughly,
after that if you want to take a depression in English, then
consult with advisors for some result,
after that you can take this decision, so
friends, thank you so much for watching this
too, friends, if you liked the video,
please subscribe to this channel
and friends, share this video with your friends,
so see you soon
friends, go to the next video.